

West Chester, PA 19382

(267) 393-3829

maxxgoulazian@gmail.com

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Currently a Biochemistry major studying at West Chester University with a minor in Health Sciences. Can offer a comprehensive background in leading experimental research activities and conducting biochemical experiments. Knowledgeable in collecting and inspecting biological samples, data collection and research, laboratory protocols, and systems evaluations and improvements. Well-versed in research processes and passionate about setting exceptional standards for medical care focused within the field of human longevity. Goals surrounding the combination of lead innovation of medication, while focusing on maximizing environmental sustainability and ecologically efficient operations.

#### **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- · Microsoft PowerPoint
- Safety and Sterility
- · Laboratory Functionality
- Analytical Chemistry

- Leadership
- Communications
- Teamwork

### CERTIFICATIONS

# Drug Development Product Management Specialization

University of California, San Diego | SKAGGS School of Pharmacy

Credential ID 9PQKD7MQUSLG

## Drug Commercialization

University of California, San Diego | SKAGGS School of Pharmacy
Credential ID HYLLX3OKGRWVW

# Drug Development

University of California, San Diego | SKAGGS School of Pharmacy

Credential ID R4NM9RQ95HM9

# **Drug Discovery**

University of California, San Diego | SKAGGS School of Pharmacy

Credential ID HDQNUEF6TRJV

# FDA Process for Approving Generic Drugs

Credential ID 1023193

# Fundamentals of Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) in Clinical Laboratories

Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Course Pace ID 288-006-20 Credential ID 1090648

# Fundamentals of Working Safely in a Biological Safety Cabinet

Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Course Pace ID 288-014-19 Credential ID 1041976

# Insanitary Conditions & Sterility Assurance

Credential ID 1092865

# Laboratory Continuity of Operations (COOP)

Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Credential ID 1067137

# Regulatory Framework for Human Drug Compounding

FDA Credential ID 1089314

Recruitment

June 2020-September 2020

#### Core Microbiology Skills

Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Credential ID 1035232

# **Emergency Distribution of Pharmaceuticals**

University of Washington Credential ID 1021346

# **Blood Borne Pathogens Training**

EAU Claire City-County Health Department Credential ID 1047781

## Fundamental Neuroscience for Neuroimaging

John Hopkins University Credential ID TT6RQZ4SVCHG

# LMBP A-6 Cycle: Review and Evaluation Methods for Quality Improvement

Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Course Pace ID 288-011-19 Credential ID 1078346

# PROFESSIONAL & WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Philanthropy

Sigma Phi Epsilon Pennsylvania Tau September 2018-September 2019

- Managed every aspect of events
- Maintained strict budgets

August 2020-October 2020

• Effective planning and expense control

Sigma Phi Epsilon Pennsylvania Tau

**New Member Coordinator** 

• Created organizational regulations

· Developed successful solutions

# Enhanced organizational systems Head of Social

Sigma Phi Epsilon Pennsylvania Tau September 2019-February 2020

• Improved future events based on planning

Sigma Phi Epsilon Pennsylvania Tau

• Reviewed and interviewed applicants

• Improved organizational policies

Developed new practices and policies

## **Fundraising**

Sigma Phi Epsilon Pennsylvania Tau September 2018-September 2019

- Kept detailed records of contacts
- Established new potential contributors
- Created long term donor relationships

#### President

Pharmaceutical Product Development Club WCU February 2021-Present

- Delegate tasks to a structured executive board
- Implement successful organization structure
- Directly influenced club growth

## **EDUCATION & AFILLIATIONS**

# West Chester University

- Bachelor's Degree in Biochemistry
- Minor in Health Sciences
- Expected Graduation May 2022
- Dean's List Fall 2020, GPA: 4.0

# Pharmaceutical Product Development Club

- West Chester University
- Active Member

# Sigma Phi Epsilon

- West Chester University
- Pennsylvania Tau Chapter
- Active Member & Leader